3zfile.net 2018-06-18

# 3zFile - upload and download your files with high speeds

## Privacy Policy

We at [3zfile.net](http://3zfile.net/) respect the privacy of our users. All information collected at [3zfile.net](http://3zfile.net/) is kept confidential and will not be sold, reused, or rented in any way. We do not share user information with any 3rd parties. We have taken the appropriate security measures to protect from loss, incorrect usage, or change of information provided to us by the users of the service. 

**IP Addresses:**

IP addresses are logged by [3zfile.net](http://3zfile.net/) to ensure account safety, features availability, measuring usage and statistical purposes.

**Email Addresses:**

We collect email addresses of users at the time of registration as means of contact and verification. [3zfile.net](http://3zfile.net/) does not rent, sell, or share your email addresses with anyone.

**Disclosures of Exceptional Kind:**

We at [3zfile.net](http://3zfile.net/) may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information suggests to actual act of violence or threatened harm or potential threats to the physical safety of any person or persons. Disclosure may also be required by law or if we receive a legal notice or similar request from authorities. Disclosure of your information can be lawful or as a result of a legal process.

**Cookies:**

[3zfile.net](http://3zfile.net/) uses cookies to store the preferences of users. 3zfile uses cookies for the users comfort in order to save the browser settings. 3zfile does not use any methods for tracking users (such as spy or gif images).

**Third-Party Cookies:**

The third-party advertisers might place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Third-Party Advertising:**

Advertisements located on our website can be posted directly or through third party advertisement firms. These companies may use information (not including your email, address, name, address, telephone numbers etc.) about your visits to this and other web sites for statistical purposes and to place an advertisement of wares and services that might be interesting to you.

**Safe operation with files:**

The appropriate security server measures are taken to protect from loss, incorrect usage of files saved on [3zfile.net.](http://3zfile.net/) Files, saved for delivery can be accessible only to 3zfile representatives or via a link provided to the recipient. **All files saved by our service are deleted after a certain time period if you do not delete them yourself.**

**Minors:**

No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by visitors under eighteen (18) years of age. Persons under eighteen (18) years of age are not permitted to access the Site and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from such individuals. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

**Acceptance and Changes to Privacy Policy:**

By using this Site and/or Services, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy. Any change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the site. Please check this page periodically for changes.
